https://ramenvalves.com/privacy-policy/

Storage tank protection
About usAbout usSustainabilityQualityEvents and exhibitionsCareers
Home / Privacy Policy
Ramén Valves privacy policy Ramén Valves is committed to ensure the privacy of everyone who uses our services. This policy sets out how we will use your personal data. This policy reflects our duties under the General Data Protection Regulation 2016 (GDPR), the Data Protection Act (1998). It describes how we use personal data, keep it secure, make sure it is accurate and uphold your rights as a data subject. This data policy was last updated in September 2019.
Who we are Ramén Valves AB is the data controller for the information you provide. Our address is:
Ramén Valves AB
Fredsforsstigen 22A
168 67 Bromma
Sweden
Our Data Protection responsible can be contacted at info@ramenvalves.com or by calling +46 8 594 779 70.
How Ramén Valves uses your personal data Personal data collected by this website will only be used for the purposes (or closely related purposes) for which it was collected.
We may use your personal information to:
Contacting you about enquiries/questions you sent us through our website forms.
Meeting our legal obligations as a registered company.
Processing your subscription to our newsletter.
Confirming your identity when you contact us.
Administer the website.
Improve your browsing experience by personalizing the website.
Enable your use of the services available on the website.
Your rights as a data subject You have rights as a data subject. These rights are:
The right to be informed – this means we must inform you how we are going to use your personal data. We do this through this privacy policy and by informing you how your data will be used each time we collect it.
The right of access – you have the right to access your personal data (e.g. data that is about you) that we hold. This is called a subject access request. We must respond to your request within one month. To request access to your data, please email info@ramenvalves.com. It is very helpful if you tell us what of your personal data you are seeking.
The right to rectification – if you think the data we hold on you is incorrect, tell us so we can put it right. You can do this by mailing info@ramenvalves.com or call +46 8 594 779 70.
The right to erasure – you have the right to request that we delete your data. We will do so, provided that we do not have a legal reason for keeping it. To request this, please email info@ramenvalves.com.
The right to data portability – you can obtain and reuse your personal data for your own purposes across different services, for example different unions. To request this, please info@ramenvalves.com.
The right to object – you have the right to object You can opt out of direct marketing (newsletter) any time by contacting us at info@ramenvalves.com.
At Ramén Valves we are committed to upholding your rights as a data subject. If you think we have not done so, please contact info@ramenvalves.com.
For how long we keep your personal information? We keep your personal information the shortest period possible to fulfill the purposes we had with gathering the information, including the purpose of fulfilling our legal obligations and accounting as a registered company.
Consent There are some types of data processing that we only do if you have given us your consent. These are:
Sending direct marketing messages by email.
If you wish to unsubscribe please follow the instructions in the sent email or contact us at info@ramenvalves.com.
Email marketing All emails that we send you are tracked.  This helps us to ensure that you only receive emails from us that are of interest to you.  You can unsubscribe from emails at any time by clicking the ‘unsubscribe’ button at the bottom of an email.
Cookies used on our website When on our website, data may be stored on a “cookie”. This is a tiny element of data that our site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your hard drive. This small amount of information does NOT contain any private information stored on your computer.
Like most websites the purpose of using cookies is to improve our users’ experience.  We ask when you first access our site if you are happy for cookies to be used. If you choose not to use cookies, it may be difficult to use some parts of our website.
Subscribe to our newsletter
Subscribe
Ramén Valves
About us
Sustainability
Quality
Contact
Privacy policy
Fredsforsstigen 22A,
168 67 Bromma
Sweden
Phone: +46 8 598 931 00
Contact us:
info@ramenvalves.com
Questions about your order?
order@ramenvalves.com
Questions about your invoice?
economy@ramenvalves.com
×
Subscribe to our newsletter!
